clef.io 2016-05-07

# Clef | Privacy Policy

### CLEF PRIVACY POLICY (Last revised on May 1, 2013)

Protecting your privacy is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Clef website and mobile application. It explains how information is collected, used, and disclosed by Clef with respect to your access and use of Clef’s services, whether through our website [www.getclef.com](http://www.getclef.com/) or Clef’s mobile application in connection with sites that integrate Clef. By using the Clef website or mobile app, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

###### Collection of your Personal Information

Clef may collect personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, phone number, and websites where you have accounts. We collect this information when you create an account, send us an email with an inquiry, and log in on the Clef website or mobile application. The collection of this personally identifiable information is frequently required for registering on new websites. Users will no longer need to type login information on each new site that integrates Clef. We track logins to help understand where our users are getting the most value from Clef and allocate our resources accordingly.

We also automatically collect certain information when you use Clef such as phone operating system, device type, and browser type in order to better support our users. This information is not treated as personal information unless we combine it with or link it to any personally identifiable information mentioned above.

Clef encourages you to review the privacy policy of websites you choose to connect though www.getclef.com in order to understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Clef is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outsides of getclef.com.

###### Use of Your Personal Information and Third Parties

Clef collects and uses your personal information to operate the Clef website and deliver the services you have requested. Clef will send one welcome email following registration to all registered users. We will periodically send service updates to registered users.

Clef does not share personally identifiable information with third parties without your permission. When you register at a new site that integrates Clef, we will notify you of what information the site requires and you must give permission in order for us to share it. Once you approve, the other site owns that information and we are not responsible for their use.

Clef does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Clef keeps track of websites users log in to using Clef. Any information you provide on those sites is shared with the owner of that site and subject to their privacy policy. Our privacy policy does not apply to such sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and/or policies of those sites.

###### Protecting Your Information

Identity protection is our business and we take it seriously. We take appropriate measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent misuse and unauthorized access. Despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.

###### Use of Cookies

The Clef website uses “cookies.” A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs on or infect your computer with viruses. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

Clef works to offer a consistent experience across the web using a cookie. This cookie is securely signed and contains only an identifier for Clef to recognize the user while they are logged in. As soon as the user logs out of Clef, none of the information in the cookie is personally identifiable.

###### Deactivation of Your Account

Deactivation removes information about the specific phone. The user can reactive an account on a different phone. Deactivation will not completely delete your Clef account.

###### Children Under Thirteen

Our service is not directed to children under thirteen and does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. If we learn that we have collected personal information of a child under thirteen, we will take the appropriate steps to delete such information form our files as soon as possible.

###### Changes to this Statement

Clef will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Clef encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Clef is protecting your information.

_Questions? Clef welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy._

**Effective: May 1, 2013**
